unishippers.com 2018-02-28

# Unishippers Privacy Statement - Unishippers

Unishippers privacy policy covers treatment of personally identifiable information that Unishippers collects when you are on Unishippers’ web site and when you use our services. This policy also includes personally identifiable information that our business partners share or may collect on Unishippers’ website.

**Sharing and Disclosure  
**Unishippers will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. Unishippers may send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:

  * We have your consent to share information or need to provide your information to provide a service requested by you.
  * We need to send the information to companies (including franchisees and licensees) who work to provide a service to you.
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process.
  * We find that your actions on our websites violate the legal terms and conditions of using this web site, or any of our usage guidelines.
  * We are using your information for Unishippers’ sales and marketing purposes. Franchisees and licensees may contact shippers and consignees to provide service or to perform sales and marketing activities. To remove yourself from our marketing list please contact [webmaster@unishippers.com](mailto:webmaster@unishippers.com).

**Cookie Usage  
**We use cookies on the website to track visitor behavior and store certain site preferences. If you prefer not to allow the use of cookies, you can change the configuration of your browser to either warn you when you receive a cookie, or to automatically reject them. You may find, however, that disabling cookies means certain areas of the site do not function correctly.

If you would like to find out more about cookies, including how to control or delete them, then we recommend you visit [http://www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) for detailed guidance.

This website also uses Google Remarketing. These cookies show relevant adverts to users who have previously visited our website and as they browse other websites.

You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [Google Ad Preferences](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated?hl=en) page, and if you want to you can opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings or permanently using a browser plugin.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy  
**Unishippers may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in this policy we will notify you by posting an announcement on our web pages at least ten (10) days before the substantial change takes effect. Other than as expressly stated above, your personally identifiable information is an asset of Unishippers and may be treated as such for all purposes.
